Finding aid to the general Faculty papers CA.MS.01007
Smith College Archives
General Faculty papers
1907-1994
Smith College Archives
Smith College--Faculty.
CA.MS.01007
8.75 linear feet (22 containers)
The collection includes group photographs, Faculty Who's Who, material on endowed chairs, clubs, shows, and committees.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials in the Smith College Archives are open for use, with the following exceptions: "Office Files," files of records created for the use of the administrative unit that created them, are closed to research for a period of 10 years following their creation. Faculty tenure and promotion files, as well as inactive faculty files are closed permanently. Minutes of the Faculty Council are closed to all except current Smith College Faculty for a period of 75 years following their creation. In all cases, the College Archives will continue to provide public access to materials that were intended to be public at the time of their creation (press releases, publications, etc.)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes group photographs, Faculty Who's Who, material on endowed chairs, clubs, shows, and committees.
Smith College -- Faculty.; Smith College.
- General, A-I (Box 640)
- Advisers (Box 640.1)
- General, M-Z (Box 640.2)
- Chairs and Lectures, Published Katherine Asher Engel lectures, 1959-1971 (Box 640.3)
- Chairs and Lectures, Published Katherine Asher Engel lectures, 1970-1994 (Box 640.4)
- Chairs and Lectures, A-H (Box 641)
- Chairs and Lectures, K-Sm (Box 642)
- Chairs and Lectures, Sp-Z (Box 643)
- Clubs, A-Z (Box 644)
- Faculty Club (Smith College Club) (Box 644.1)
- The Club, 1907-1975 (Box 645)
- The Monday Club, 1975-1985 (Box 645)
- Committees, A-Z (Box 646.2)
- Organizations, AAUP, 1916-1933 (Box 647.4)
- Organizations, AAUP, 1933-1969 (Box 648)
- Photographs (Box 648.1)
- Shows, 1923-1949 (Box 648.2)
- Shows, 1950-1958 (Box 649)
- Shows, 1960- (Box 650)
- Yellow cards, A-L (Box 651)
- Yellow cards, M-R (Box 652)
- Yellow cards, S-Z (Box 653)
- Staff, Union (SEIU) (Box 653.1)